<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rubber on BridgeScorer</title>
    <link>/rubber.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rubber on BridgeScorer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 22:59:40 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/rubber/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>List</title>
      <link>/rubber/list.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 18:15:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rubber/list.html</guid>
      <description>This shows all the past Rubber Bridge matches that have been played.
For each match, the start and end time and all the players scores are shown, higher scores to the left. The Delete button is used to delete a match. The button in the Id column goes to the summary page for that match.
The New button is used to start a new Rubber Bridge match. This will bring up the enter names page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Names</title>
      <link>/rubber/names.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 18:17:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rubber/names.html</guid>
      <description>Enter the players names in their corresponding position, and select the dealer for the first hand. Then hit the OK button. The Enter Hand page is then displayed.
The Reset button clears out all the names and unselects the dealer.
The Cancel button is used to leave this page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enter Hand</title>
      <link>/rubber/hand.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 11:21:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rubber/hand.html</guid>
      <description>This page allows the scorekeeper to enter the contract that was bit for the hand, and the result of playing the hand.
For the contract and results buttons, the color of the button has the following meaning:
 The dark yellow   buttons indicates what should be selected next. The light yellow   buttons indicates that this still needs to be selected, but something else should be selected first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary</title>
      <link>/rubber/summary.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 18:17:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rubber/summary.html</guid>
      <description>This page shows the results of the Rubber Bridge match.
In the first table gives a simplified view of the results. Typically it is the same as it would be on paper.
The second table show details about each hand. The last two columns are the two teams. Number prefixed with an H are honor points, numbers in parentheses are score above the line. Numbers without any adornments are scores below the line.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>